export const data=[
    {
    question: "Which device is required for the Internet connection ?",
    option1: "Modem",
    option2: "Router",
    option3: "LAN Cable",
    option4: "Pen Drive",
    ans:1,
    },
    {
        question: "Who was then president before current presedent ?",
        option1: "Pranav Mukhopadhay",
        option2: "Ram Nath Kovind",
        option3: "Draupadi Murmu",
        option4: "Jagdip Dhankhar",
        ans:2,
        },
    {
        question: "A computer cannot BOOT if it does not have the  ?",
        option1: "Application Software",
        option2: "Internet",
        option3: "Operating System",
        option4: "Mouse",
        ans:3,
        },
        {
            question: "Ayodhya Ram Mandir inaugarated on which date ?",
            option1: "5th Jan 2024",
            option2: "2nd July 2022 ",
            option3: "22nd Jan 2024",
            option4: "13th Mar 2023",
            ans:3,
            },
        {
            question: "Which continent has the highest number of countries ?",
            option1: "Asia",
            option2: "Europe",
            option3: "North America",
            option4: "Africa",
            ans:4,
            },
            {
                question: "What is our National bird ?",
                option1: "Peacock",
                option2: "Ostrich",
                option3: "Sparrow",
                option4: "Pegion",
                ans:1,
                },
            {
                question: "First page of Website is termed as ?",
                option1: "Index Page",
                option2: "Homepage",
                option3: "Sitmap",
                option4: "Pen Drive",
                ans:2,
                },
                {
                    question: "How many spokes are there in Ashoka Chakra ?",
                    option1: "22",
                    option2: "12",
                    option3: "56",
                    option4: "24",
                    ans:4,
                    },
                {
                question: "Junk e-mail is also called ?",
                option1: "Spam",
                option2: "Fake",
                option3: "Archived",
                option4: "Bin",
                ans:1,
                },
                {
                    question: "Which is world's largest flower ?",
                    option1: "Rafflesia arnoldi",
                    option2: "Wolffia globasa",
                    option3: "Corse flower",
                    option4: "Titan Arum",
                    ans:1,
                    },
]
